<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BEST</string>
    <string name="instructionsButton">Instructions</string>
    <string name="settingsAction">Subtask Settings</string>
    <string name="loadprofileButton">Load Profile</string>
    <string name="createprofileButton">Create Profile</string>
    <string name="exportButton">Export Data</string>
    <string name="infoAction">Additional Information</string>
    <string name="additionalInfoText"><big><b>\nContact\n\n</b></big><ul><li>Ciaran Considine: Ciaran.Considine@vanderbilt.edu\n\n</li><li>Chris Abeare: Cabeare@uwindsor.ca\n\n</li><li>Humza Khan: humza.adil.khan@gmail.com\n\n</li></ul><big><b>User Permissions\n\n</b></big><ul><li>Universities, Foundations, Health Professionals, Clinics, Public Health Institutes:\n\nThe BEST may be used WITHOUT permission for all clinical, educational, and research purposes, WITH proper citation.\n\n</li><li>Commercial Entities, Pharma:\n\nPlease contact the authors.\n\n\n</li></ul><big><b>Citation Information\n\n</b></big>Considine, C.M. &amp; Abeare, C.A. (2015). Brief Estimate of Seconds Test (BEST). Unpublished instrument.\n\nMalleck, M., Considine, C.M., Freund, S., &amp; Abeare, C.A. (2016, February). The Brief Estimate of Seconds Test (BEST): A pilot study examining initial psychometrics and norms for a new chronometric clinical test. Poster presented at the International Neuropsychological Society convention, Boston, MA.\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="defaultAllAction">Restore Defaults</string>
    <string name="newProfileSaveAction">Save Profile</string>
    <string name="rveInstructions">In a moment, I will press “Begin” and a tone will sound. When you hear the tone, please close your eyes and sit quietly until I give you further instruction.\n\n\nAgain, when I press “Begin” and you hear a tone, you will close your eyes and do nothing until I give you further instruction.\n\n\nDo you have any questions?</string>
    <string name="rveDone">Examiner say: OPEN YOUR EYES.\nTell me your best guess at how much time passed while your eyes were closed.\nUse the field below, be as specific as you can.</string>
    <string name="preInstructions">In a moment, I am going to press “Begin.” A first tone will sound, then after some time has passed, a second tone will sound.\n\nThen, it is your turn – I want you to use the button on the screen to make a tone, then wait the same amount of time before you press the button to make a second tone.\n\nYou will be trying to recreate the same pause between my two tones. Does that make sense?\n\nPlease do not speak, nor tap your hand or foot, just keep track in your head. Do you have any questions?</string>
    <string name="pveInstructions">In a moment, I am going to press “Begin,” and a tone will play. After some time, you will hear a second tone.\n\n\nI want you to tell me how many seconds passed between the two tones.\n\n\nPlease do not speak, nor tap your hand or foot during the time, just keep track in your head.\n\n\nDo you have any questions?</string>
    <string name="ppeInstructions">In a moment, I am going to give you a certain amount of time. I want you to press the button to make a tone, wait the amount of time I tell you, and then press the button a second time after you think that amount of time has passed.\n\nPlease do not speak, nor tap your hand or foot during the time, just keep track in your head.\n\nDo you have any questions?</string>
    <string name="rbeInstructions">In a moment, I will press Begin and a button will appear on the screen. It will begin to blink and beep at a regular pace.\n\n\nI want you to keep pressing the button at the same time as the blink/beep, learning the rhythm.\n\n\nAfter a bit of time, the blinking and beeping will stop, but I want you to keep pressing the button at the same rhythm that you learned. Keep doing this until the button disappears. Do you have any questions?\n\nNOTE: The button will beep 20 times before recording the next 60 taps.</string>
    <string name="Instructions">\nThe BEST is composed of 5 subtasks, designed to measure the cognitive task of time perception (chronognosis).\n\nTime-targets for each task can be manually altered by tapping the settings button in the main menu, though doing so will preclude being able to compare the raw scores to established normative data.\n\nTasks will progress sequentially automatically, but an examiner can navigate the subtasks using the arrows at the bottom of the screen if needed.\n\nFor each task, examinee instructions will be displayed on the screen. These should be read aloud to the examinee if necessary.\n\nOnce the examinee confirms understanding the instructions, the examiner should press the “Begin” button, initiating the task.\n\nThe screen will allow examinee/examiner information entry as appropriate.\n\nDuring each trial, there are two buttons that allow for re-administration as needed: The “Cancel” button (X in the top left), which resets the present subtask to its instruction page, and the “Re-administer” button (looping arrow in the top right), which immediately restarts the current subtask.\n\nIf the individual breaks a rule or breaks protocol, stop the trial, explain the instructions again, and re-do the trial. Discontinue the SUBTASK only if the individual cannot comprehend instructions after two attempts (try next subtask).\n\n<b><u>Note: Make sure no clocks are visible OR audible.</u></b>\n</string>
    <string name="BESTComplete"><big>BEST Complete\n\n</big>Please return the device to the examiner.</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="sort_ascending">Sort Ascending</string>
    <string name="sort_descending">Sort Descending</string>
    <string name="clear_sorting">Clear</string>
    <string name="row_show">Show 5. Row</string>
    <string name="row_hide">Hide 5. Row</string>

</resources>
